Welcome
This is one of many videos I will post that demonstrate video creation techniques.
The video effects are all created with FFmpeg and JavaScript.
The actual creations are often screen captures using FFmpeg.
Gimp or Krita are used to process images.
Both are FREE and open source programs as is FFmpeg.
I am a Linux user, however FFmpeg, Gimp and Krita work on Windows also.
Github/jupyterjones, mylinuxtoybox.com, GoogleDrive will all be used,
to make the various source code for the video projects available.
There also will be FREE suites available that can be used for your video creation.
Quite often scripts can be reused, by only changing videos names and timing.
It is my wish that this YouTube Channel and my website
will become an interactive experience with subscribers.
Videos posted will cover a range of computer languages and skills.
Many videos will be screen captures of coding hints and ideas.
Basically, me playing on my computer.
I used the MyLinuxToyBox because I did not want to provide structured lessons.
I plan on recording my activities with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python
Ruby, VPS services, SSH, FFmpeg, Flask, SQL and SQLite3
Bash Scripting, Docker, Artificial intelligence just to name
a few computer activities.
I love Jupyter Notebooks
Jupyter Notebooks have a multitude of uses
I do not only use them to test and run Python code
I also use them as a text editor, image editor, to run JavaScript
I use them to access and edit SQLLite3 ad Mongo Databases.
There is so much to show I get excited to think about it.
I wish to share what I have learned and waht I am learning at this time.
YouTube and my website are the best tools to do this.
To Non-Linux users I will show the the easiest ans safest way to
play with Linux.
Subscribe and PLAY WITH ME.